freeringers.net 2007-06-17

# Privacy Policy > FreeRingers.net

How To Contact Us

**Our Commitment To Privacy:**  
Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this policy explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this policy easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested. 

**The Information We Collect:**  
This policy applies to all information collected or submitted on the FreeRingers website. On some pages, you can order products or make requests. The types of personal information collected at these pages are: 

Name  
Email address  
Cellular phone number  

**How We Use Information:**  
We use the information you provide about yourself when placing an order only to complete that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order. 

We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties. 

We use your cellular phone number to relay files to your phone that you request. The phone numbers are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties. 

We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website. 

We may use emails for testimonials and marketing. We will only identify the testimonial as the sender's first name and last initial. 

Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above. 

**Credit Card Information:**  
We use the outside company PayPal (global leader in online payments) to process credit card and all other types of orders. Because we utilize an outside company, we never receive any type of credit card information. The only information we receive is the confirmation of the order, the buyer's name and email address. At no time do we ever get the credit card number. PayPal uses secured pages when entering credit card or other personal information. Please review [PayPal's Privacy Policy](http://www.paypal.com/cgi-bin/webscr?cmd=p/gen/ua/policy_privacy-outside). 

**Our Commitment To Data Security:**  
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. 

**Our Commitment To Children's Privacy:**  
Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13. 

**How To Access Or Correct Your Information:**  
You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by accessing the "Your Information" menu item in the member's area. We use this procedure to better safeguard your information. 

You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by using the "Change Email" menu item in the member's area. 

To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections. 

**How To Contact Us:**  
Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please contact us.
